{
    "subject": "resource/Samuel_Fitch",
    "predicate": "property/shortDescription",
    "object": "Connecticut politician",
    "human_readable": "Samuel Fitch was a Connecticut politician.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9651831984519958,
            "question": "What was Samuel Fitch's role in Connecticut politics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9168602228164673,
            "question": "In what state was Samuel Fitch a politician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6757761836051941,
            "question": "Was Samuel Fitch involved in government?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6146005392074585,
            "question": "Do you know any specific events related to Samuel Fitch's political career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6068920493125916,
            "question": "What profession was Samuel Fitch known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.490964412689209,
            "question": "Was Samuel Fitch a well-known figure in his time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4552536606788635,
            "question": "What is Samuel Fitch remembered for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4480333924293518,
            "question": "Where did Samuel Fitch live?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4337610900402069,
            "question": "What kind of work did Samuel Fitch do?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3560332953929901,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Samuel Fitch's career?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Samuel Fitch was a Connecticut politician.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3577_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of work did Samuel Fitch do?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3577_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Samuel Fitch live?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3577_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Samuel Fitch remembered for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3577_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3577_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3577_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3577_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3577_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3577_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3577_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3577_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3577_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3577_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3577_72.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the provided context information, I can confirm that the statement is indeed supported by the documents.\n\nHere is the structured JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\nThe first document mentions Samuel Fitch as \"a member of the House of Representatives of the Colony of Connecticut\" which supports the statement."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Samuel Fitch's political activities, such as his membership in the House of Representatives of the Colony of Connecticut. This supports the statement that Samuel Fitch was a Connecticut politician."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}